<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Romance on Sam Feldstein</title>
    <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/tags/romance/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Romance on Sam Feldstein</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 20:23:25 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://samfeldstein.xyz/tags/romance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Not the Story&#39;s Fault You Thought You Were Still on the Ranch</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/lonesome-dove/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 20:23:25 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/lonesome-dove/</guid>
      <description>These aren&#39;t young soldiers Lonesome Dove is a story about the lust for adventure, a force so powerful it can rip you from the arms of comfort and chuck you into the jaws of death. Daredevils everywhere will relate to Gus and Woodrow. They are men who can&#39;t stand to sit still. Nobody makes them leave Lonesome Dove. They leave because they&#39;re bored. Thus, their subsequent wounds are self-inflicted. These guys aren&#39;t naive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cinderella in Reverse: &#39;Roman Holiday&#39;</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/roman-holiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:46:44 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/roman-holiday/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps it’s her eyes, or how her expression always bespeaks the shadow of a smile, even when she’s crying, but we warm to Princess Ann straightaway. Of course it helps that she’s young and Audrey Hepburn, but really it has to do with the way we meet her; in the midst of a lengthy and exhausting royal public relations tour of Europe. By the time she finally finishes shaking the hands of an endless entourage of aristocrats and (one presumes) eligible bachelors, she has us completely.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
