<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sam Feldstein</title>
    <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sam Feldstein</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:47:14 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://samfeldstein.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I’m Sam Feldstein and I write stories. I&amp;rsquo;m fond of blogs, books, movies, and photography. I&amp;rsquo;m interested in writing, storytelling, web design, Judaism, and economics. The best way to keep up with my work is to subscribe to my newsletter or rss feed. If you&amp;rsquo;d like to get in touch, you can email me at samfeldstein@proton.me. You can also find me on Instagram, Mastodon, and Letterboxd.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Published Writing</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/published-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/published-writing/</guid>
      <description>Fiction Queen of the Thunderbeasts on the DMsGuild (roleplaying adventure, 2023)
&amp;ldquo;The First&amp;rdquo; in The Collidescope (flash fiction, Oct. 2022)
&amp;ldquo;The Man Who Was a Boy Made of Memories&amp;rdquo; in The Chamber (short story, Nov. 2021)
Not Fiction &amp;ldquo;Big Bend Reproductive Coalition launches community needs assessment&amp;rdquo; in The Big Bend Sentinel (article, Aug. 2023)
&amp;ldquo;Trans-Pecos Festival of Music + Love doubles as platform for advocacy and outreach&amp;rdquo; in The Big Bend Sentinel (article, Oct.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Digest</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/digest-23-12-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:47:14 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/digest-23-12-04/</guid>
      <description>News My big update is that this website exists. I&amp;rsquo;ve been flirting with blogging for years now, but I&amp;rsquo;ve never committed to it. I&amp;rsquo;ve created and deleted several websites&amp;mdash;mostly out of self-consciousness and an inability to decide how to spend my time&amp;mdash;but this one looks like it&amp;rsquo;s here to stay. I&amp;rsquo;m really happy with how it turned out. I&amp;rsquo;ve been slowly learning HTML, CSS, and JavaScript over the last two years or so, first via The Odin Project and then MDN Web Docs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo Sorting and My First Gambling Foray</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/buffalo-sorting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:57:28 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/buffalo-sorting/</guid>
      <description>Early October I went to South Dakota for the first time since I was a kid. I have a friend from college whose parents own a cabin in the Black Hills which she and her boyfriend (also a college friend) go to a few times a year, and I’d been talking about going with them for some time. I landed in Sioux Falls. My friends were driving from Des Moines, so it worked out that they could pick me up from the airport and we set out from there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riddled with Words: &#39;The Maltese Falcon&#39;</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/maltese-falcon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:37:34 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/maltese-falcon/</guid>
      <description>Sam Spade exhibits a degree of unhinged lunacy on par with Hamlet, and there’s something to that, isn’t there, because you know what they have in common? They’re both damaged goods. Hamlet’s uncle killed his father and then had shameless carnal relations with his mother. It’s enough to drive anyone to San Francisco, and Sam, well we don’t know what he’s been through but part of the art of filmmaking as John Huston so deftly demonstrates is knowing what to say and when to say it, yes, but also knowing what not to say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cinderella in Reverse: &#39;Roman Holiday&#39;</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/roman-holiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:46:44 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/roman-holiday/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps it’s her eyes, or how her expression always bespeaks the shadow of a smile, even when she’s crying, but we warm to Princess Ann straightaway. Of course it helps that she’s young and Audrey Hepburn, but really it has to do with the way we meet her; in the midst of a lengthy and exhausting royal public relations tour of Europe. By the time she finally finishes shaking the hands of an endless entourage of aristocrats and (one presumes) eligible bachelors, she has us completely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Absence of Meaning in &#39;The Lighthouse&#39;</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/the-lighthouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 00:28:19 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/the-lighthouse/</guid>
      <description>All movies have to become real, on some level, in order to do their good work, and some of them can only achieve this by taking active steps to distance themselves from reality. All movies do this to some extent simply by appearing on a screen, but some of them, as with The Lighthouse, need a little more than that. Eggers’s choice to shoot on 35mm negative in an aspect ratio of 1.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Other Stuff</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/other-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/other-stuff/</guid>
      <description>Notebook My digital workspace, where I keep notes, project documents, and other adversaria.
Like Father Like Son Like Movies A podcast I host with my dad. As you can probably tell, it&amp;rsquo;s about movies. You can find us on Apple Podcasts or your podcatcher of choice.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
