<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Sam Feldstein</title>
    <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Sam Feldstein</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 08:53:53 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://samfeldstein.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building an Automatic File-Mover with ChatGPT</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/file-mover/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 08:53:53 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/file-mover/</guid>
      <description>Once a month I back up my Goodreads library to a folder on my computer called exports. The process: Go to the website, find the Export button, download the file, open the terminal, move the file from Downloads to exports. It&#39;s not enough of a pain for me not to do it, but it is enough of a pain for me to try to make it easier. I figured there had to be an extant solution, but rather than hunt around the internet for an appropriate application, I decided to build one myself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Digest</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/digest-23-12-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 10:00:19 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/digest-23-12-11/</guid>
      <description>New post(s) alert In case you missed them, I wrote two new posts this week: a short one about Talmudic wisdom in The Exorcist (the book, not the movie) and a longer one about shock and Lonesome Dove (the movie, not the book). (It&#39;s actually a miniseries but I really wanted to capitalize on that symmetry just now.)&#xA;New publication(s) alert This week I have the pleasure of announcing that my short story &amp;quot;The Man Who Was a Boy Made of Memories&amp;quot; was just published on the Tales to Terrify podcast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Not the Story&#39;s Fault You Thought You Were Still on the Ranch</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/lonesome-dove/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 20:23:25 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/lonesome-dove/</guid>
      <description>These aren&#39;t young soldiers Lonesome Dove is a story about the lust for adventure, a force so powerful it can rip you from the arms of comfort and chuck you into the jaws of death. Daredevils everywhere will relate to Gus and Woodrow. They are men who can&#39;t stand to sit still. Nobody makes them leave Lonesome Dove. They leave because they&#39;re bored. Thus, their subsequent wounds are self-inflicted. These guys aren&#39;t naive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>And God Said, &#39;Care, Dammit&#39;</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/care-dammit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 10:00:46 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/care-dammit/</guid>
      <description>I was working on a short story about an exorcist (which I&#39;ve since abandoned) so I decided to read The Exorcist. I&#39;ve seen the movie but can&#39;t say I&#39;m a fan. The book is excellent. One passage stood out. It&#39;s said by Merrin, the senior exorcist, to Damien, the amateur who&#39;s been having a crisis of faith:&#xA;Long ago I despaired of ever loving my neighbor. Certain people repelled me. How could I love them?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Digest</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/digest-23-12-04/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 21:47:14 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/digest-23-12-04/</guid>
      <description>News My big update is that this website exists. I&#39;ve been flirting with blogging for years now, but I&#39;ve never committed to it. I&#39;ve created and deleted several websites--mostly out of self-consciousness and an inability to decide how to spend my time--but this one looks like it&#39;s here to stay. I&#39;m really happy with how it turned out. I&#39;ve been slowly learning HTML, CSS, and JavaScript over the last two years or so, first via The Odin Project and then MDN Web Docs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo Sorting and My First Gambling Foray</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/buffalo-sorting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Nov 2023 22:57:28 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/buffalo-sorting/</guid>
      <description>Early October I went to South Dakota for the first time since I was a kid. I have a friend from college whose parents own a cabin in the Black Hills which she and her boyfriend (also a college friend) go to a few times a year, and I’d been talking about going with them for some time. I landed in Sioux Falls. My friends were driving from Des Moines, so it worked out that they could pick me up from the airport and we set out from there.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post 3</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 11:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/post-3/</guid>
      <description>Occaecat aliqua consequat laborum ut ex aute aliqua culpa quis irure esse magna dolore quis. Proident fugiat labore eu laboris officia Lorem enim. Ipsum occaecat cillum ut tempor id sint aliqua incididunt nisi incididunt reprehenderit. Voluptate ad minim sint est aute aliquip esse occaecat tempor officia qui sunt. Aute ex ipsum id ut in est velit est laborum incididunt. Aliqua qui id do esse sunt eiusmod id deserunt eu nostrud aute sit ipsum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post 2</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/post-2/</guid>
      <description>Anim eiusmod irure incididunt sint cupidatat. Incididunt irure irure irure nisi ipsum do ut quis fugiat consectetur proident cupidatat incididunt cillum. Dolore voluptate occaecat qui mollit laborum ullamco et. Ipsum laboris officia anim laboris culpa eiusmod ex magna ex cupidatat anim ipsum aute. Mollit aliquip occaecat qui sunt velit ut cupidatat reprehenderit enim sunt laborum. Velit veniam in officia nulla adipisicing ut duis officia.&#xA;Exercitation voluptate irure in irure tempor mollit Lorem nostrud ad officia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Riddled with Words: &#39;The Maltese Falcon&#39;</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/maltese-falcon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:37:34 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/maltese-falcon/</guid>
      <description>Sam Spade exhibits a degree of unhinged lunacy on par with Hamlet, and there’s something to that, isn’t there, because you know what they have in common? They’re both damaged goods. Hamlet’s uncle killed his father and then had shameless carnal relations with his mother. It’s enough to drive anyone to San Francisco, and Sam, well we don’t know what he’s been through but part of the art of filmmaking as John Huston so deftly demonstrates is knowing what to say and when to say it, yes, but also knowing what not to say.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cinderella in Reverse: &#39;Roman Holiday&#39;</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/roman-holiday/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:46:44 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/roman-holiday/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps it’s her eyes, or how her expression always bespeaks the shadow of a smile, even when she’s crying, but we warm to Princess Ann straightaway. Of course it helps that she’s young and Audrey Hepburn, but really it has to do with the way we meet her; in the midst of a lengthy and exhausting royal public relations tour of Europe. By the time she finally finishes shaking the hands of an endless entourage of aristocrats and (one presumes) eligible bachelors, she has us completely.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post 1</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/post-1/</guid>
      <description>Tempor proident minim aliquip reprehenderit dolor et ad anim Lorem duis sint eiusmod. Labore ut ea duis dolor. Incididunt consectetur proident qui occaecat incididunt do nisi Lorem. Tempor do laborum elit laboris excepteur eiusmod do. Eiusmod nisi excepteur ut amet pariatur adipisicing Lorem.&#xA;Occaecat nulla excepteur dolore excepteur duis eiusmod ullamco officia anim in voluptate ea occaecat officia. Cillum sint esse velit ea officia minim fugiat. Elit ea esse id aliquip pariatur cupidatat id duis minim incididunt ea ea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Absence of Meaning in &#39;The Lighthouse&#39;</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/the-lighthouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2022 00:28:19 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/blog/the-lighthouse/</guid>
      <description>All movies have to become real, on some level, in order to do their good work, and some of them can only achieve this by taking active steps to distance themselves from reality. All movies do this to some extent simply by appearing on a screen, but some of them, as with The Lighthouse, need a little more than that. Eggers’s choice to shoot on 35mm negative in an aspect ratio of 1.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
