<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sam Feldstein</title>
    <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/tags/writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in writing on Sam Feldstein</description>
    <generator>Hugo 0.121.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 08:54:20 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://samfeldstein.xyz/tags/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is Rain?</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/what-is-rain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2024 08:54:20 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/what-is-rain/</guid>
      <description>In college I took a poetry seminar, not because I had any interest in poetry, but because I thought it would be easy. (Not that it&amp;rsquo;s important, but I was right. There was no homework. We didn&amp;rsquo;t even have to write poetry.) The professor&amp;rsquo;s name was Ryan Tucker. He was an adjunct, I think, and couldn&amp;rsquo;t have been much older than I am now. Often he&amp;rsquo;d begin class with a video or a song, sometimes to illustrate a point, but also because he apparently thought learning should be fun, a virtue I would appreciate long before I came to recognize it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mining and Refining: The Two Modes of Writing</title>
      <link>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/spontaneity-codified/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2024 09:34:12 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://samfeldstein.xyz/posts/spontaneity-codified/</guid>
      <description>There are two modes of writing: mining and refining. You&amp;rsquo;re either digging for coal, or pressing it into diamonds.&#xA;When you mine, you search for raw material. That might look like brainstorming, it might look like research, it might look like eavesdropping. It might look like nothing. You&amp;rsquo;re watching a movie and it sparks a notion, you write it down.&#xA;That last example is a little different from the others. It feels passive.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>